{
  "source": "HungryRaccoonStudios/SampleCards",
  "title": "knock knock jokes",
  "description": "funny knock knock jokes",
  "flashcards": [
    {
      "cardfront": "knock knock - who's there? - lettuce. - lettuce who?",
      "cardback": "lettuce in, it's freezing out here!"
    },
    {
      "cardfront": "knock knock - who's there? - cow says. - cow says who?",
      "cardback": "no silly, cow says mooo!"
    },
    {
      "cardfront": "knock knock - who's there? - Atch. - Atch who?",
      "cardback": "Bless you!"
    },
    {
      "cardfront": "knock knock - who's there? - Boo. - Boo who?",
      "cardback": "Don't cry, it's just a joke!"
    },
    {
      "cardfront": "knock knock - who's there? - Olive. - Olive who?",
      "cardback": "Olive your jokes are so funny!"
    },
    {
      "cardfront": "knock knock - who's there? - Lettuce. - Lettuce who?",
      "cardback": "Lettuce in, it's too cold out here!"
    },
    {
      "cardfront": "knock knock - who's there? - Hawaii. - Hawaii who?",
      "cardback": "I'm good, Hawaii you?"
    },
    {
      "cardfront": "knock knock - who's there? - Tank. - Tank who?",
      "cardback": "You're welcome!"
    },
    {
      "cardfront": "knock knock - who's there? - Cows go. - Cows go who?",
      "cardback": "No silly, cows go moo!"
    },
    {
      "cardfront": "knock knock - who's there? - Butter. - Butter who?",
      "cardback": "Butter open up, or I'll keep knocking!"
    },
    {
      "cardfront": "knock knock - who's there? - Orange. - Orange who?",
      "cardback": "Orange you glad you started this joke?"
    },
    {
      "cardfront": "knock knock - who's there? - Alpaca. - Alpaca who?",
      "cardback": "Alpaca the suitcase, you load up the car!"
    },
    {
      "cardfront": "knock knock - who's there? - Iva. - Iva who?",
      "cardback": "Iva sore hand from knocking!"
    }
  ]
}
